Guide to the Stampless lettersheet collection, 1803-1856.
Stampless lettersheet collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Stampless lettersheet collection, 1803-1856.
6933
Cornell University.Collection of Regional History.
.3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Miscellaneous letters and documents, primarily stampless lettersheets, from New York State and elsewhere include family letters, business letters, and legal documents. Also a few envelopes, stampless and stamped.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Miscellaneous letters and documents, primarily stampless lettersheets, from New York State and elsewhere include family letters, business letters, and legal documents. Also a few envelopes, stampless and stamped.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.
Subjects:
Family--New York (State); History, Local--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Allen, William Fitch (1808-1878), 1840-1846 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- B miscellaneous, 1829-1852, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Beardsley, Samuel (1790-1860), 1824-1837 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- C miscellaneous, 1817-1853 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- D miscellaneous papers, 1834, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- E miscellaneous papers, 1818-1837, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Finch & Stowell (Stowell, John C. 1817-?; Finch, Miles), Ithaca, NY, 1846-1851 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- F miscellaneous papers, 1837-1842 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- G miscellaneous papers, 1832-1844, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- H miscellaneous papers, 1816-1852, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- J miscellaneous papers, 1846-1849, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- K miscellaneous papers, 1806-1844 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- L miscellaneous papers, 1823-1844, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- M miscellaneous papers, 1809-1848, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- N and O miscellaneous papers, 1804-1845 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Price & Clapp (Price, James; Clapp, William M.), Oxford, NY, 1812-1814 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- P miscellaneous papers, 1803-1847, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Quin, E, 1844 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- R miscellaneous papers, 1834-1856 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- S miscellaneous papers, 1812-1854, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- T and U miscellaneous papers, 1815-1841, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- V miscellaneous papers, 1839-1845 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- W miscellaneous papers, 1832-1850 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Fragments of letters, 1834-1837 (Box 1, Folder 24)